Character Roster:

Types needed: 
◘zoner			(lowest health, higher projectle damage, slightly weaker melee damage, faster than average movement speed)
◘Grappler		(Slightly higher health, stronger melee damage, lower zonal damage, Average movement speed)
◘Tank			(Highest health, average melee damage, no zonal damage, Slowest movement)
◘ninja			(lower health, fastest movement, lower zonal damage, higher than average melee damage)